<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title><![CDATA[Philosophy Publics - Notes]]></title>
    <link>https://philosophypublics.substack.com</link>
    <description><![CDATA[Latest notes from Philosophy Publics]]></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:05:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:05:45 GMT</pubDate>
    <generator>Notes to RSS Feed Generator v1.0</generator>
    <atom:link href="https://alfonsotech.github.io/philosophy-publics-rss-feeds/notes-rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[This image is nauseating and shocking and entirely unsurp...]]></title>
      <link>https://philosophypublics.substack.com/notes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This image is nauseating and shocking and entirely unsurprising to anyone who&#39;s been paying attention https://katemanne.substack.com/p/the-actual-conspiracy-theory-surrounding]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:46:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">note-item-6-1757368008000</guid>
      <author>Mona Mona</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[In case there has been any doubt….]]></title>
      <link>https://philosophypublics.substack.com/notes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In case there has been any doubt….]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:39:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">note-item-8-1757363972000</guid>
      <author>Mona Mona</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[I’ve covered the Pompeii frescoes a few times over the pa...]]></title>
      <link>https://philosophypublics.substack.com/notes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[I’ve covered the Pompeii frescoes a few times over the past year. The ones you’re looking at are:

1. A fresco located in the House of Menander in Pompeii, an ancient Roman residential complex destroyed in the eruption of Vesuvius in 79 CE.

2. A fresco from the Villa of the Mysteries, a suburban villa just outside Pompeii. The frescoes, especially those in Room 5, are believed to depict initiation rites of the Dionysiac mystery cult, devoted to Dionysus (Bacchus in Roman mythology), the god of wine and ecstasy.

3. The fresco titled “Diana the Huntress,” which originated from the House of Stabia in Pompeii and dates to the 1st century BC.

4. The fresco of Flora (also called The Flora of Stabiae or Flora Primavera), a fresco from the 1st century AD. It was discovered in the excavations of Villa Arianna in Stabiae, near Pompeii, and is now housed in the Naples National Archaeological Museum.

Correct attribution and historical context are essential, especially for anyone interested in doing further research. ]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:57:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">note-item-7-1757357850000</guid>
      <author>Mona Mona</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[According to Nishida’s logic of place, opposites coexist ...]]></title>
      <link>https://philosophypublics.substack.com/notes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to Nishida’s logic of place, opposites coexist within a larger field. Rather than asking whether AI agents are human-like, the question may be: In what places do humans and machines co-evolve?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:21:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">note-item-1-1757352068000</guid>
      <author>Mona Mona</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Check out my latest essay, on capitalism and Palestine. h...]]></title>
      <link>https://philosophypublics.substack.com/notes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Check out my latest essay, on capitalism and Palestine.

https://open.substack.com/pub/marxandfriends/p/on-the-backs-of-the-arabs?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=android&amp;r=1yyj49]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">note-item-5-1757343786000</guid>
      <author>Mona Mona</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[In searching for assisted living homes for my leftist, ro...]]></title>
      <link>https://philosophypublics.substack.com/notes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In searching for assisted living homes for my leftist, rock and roll, former hippie/brown beret/ERA movement marching intellectual parents (80s), I have found a complete market hole. The existing places all still operate on an outdated 1950s idea of what older Americans are and want. My folks hate the “square, crew cut” vibe in these places. They don&#39;t want to wear funny flag hats on July 4th and watch Gunsmoke after meatloaf dinner. They want groovy hot tubs and weed brownies and flower power and reruns of MASH after eating Ethiopian with their fingers. They want Woody Gutherie sing-alongs, condoms in the crafting room, and VW Bus outings to No Kings protests, not the Casino and Lawrence Welk. I want to open a chain of old folks homes for the generation that swore to never trust anyone over 30.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 05:19:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">note-item-4-1757308762000</guid>
      <author>Mona Mona</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[It's wild how ‘feminist issues’ are still so often treate...]]></title>
      <link>https://philosophypublics.substack.com/notes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It&#39;s wild how ‘feminist issues’ are still so often treated as niche, as if we’re not literally talking about, you know, only half the world&#39;s population (and sometimes all of it.)]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">note-item-2-1756137605000</guid>
      <author>Mona Mona</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>